"迷失" 前情提要...
Previously on "Lost"...
- 他是谁?  - 他叫Richard Alpert
- Who is he?  - His name is Richard Alpert.
是个... 顾问
He's a kind of... advisor.
他干这行已经很久了
And he has had that job for a very, very long time.
你为何想死?
Why do you want to die?
我将我...
I devoted my life...
长到你无法想象的生命...
longer than you can possibly imagine...
奉献给那个
in service of a man
告诉我事出皆有因的人
who told me that everything was happening for a reason,
他说他有一个计划... 我也在计划之内...
that he had a plan... a plan that I was a part of...
但现在那个人死了 所以我为何想死?
And now that man's gone. So why do I want to die?
因为我发现 我已经失去生活的目标了
Because I just found out my entire life had no purpose.
抱歉 我无法使你快速康复
很高兴见到你...
我来 是因为我需要你的帮忙
I'm here because I need your help.
Ilana 你会帮我吗?
Will you help me, Ilana?
嗯
Yes.
我要你帮我保护6个人
There're six people I need you to protect.
我会把他们的名单给你
I'm gonna give you a list of their names.
要你帮忙的就是这事
This is what you've been preparing for.
这些人... 是谁?
These people... who are they?
他们是保留下来的接班人
They're the remaining candidates.
接班人?
Candidates?
什么接班人?
Candidates for what?
接替Jacob的人
To replace Jacob.
他说我是其中之一
She said I was one of them.
你也是 还有Hurley也是
And so are you, and so is Hurley.
哦 这敢情好 那我们现在该干嘛?
Well, that's great. So what do we do now?
我不知道
I don't know.
那谁知道?
Then who does?
等我把他们带去寺庙后...
After I've brought them to the temple...
我该干什么?
what do I do?
问Ricardus
Ask Ricardus.
他知道接下来该怎么做
He'll know what to do next.
Ricardus是谁?
Who's Ricardus?
就是他
He is.
那么 Richard...
So, Richard...
我们接下来该干嘛?
what do we do next?
我不知道"我们"接下来要干嘛
I have no idea what "we" do next.
你没告诉你的朋友们
You didn't tell your friends
当你找到我的时候 我正打算自杀么?
that I was trying to kill myself when you found me?
这听上去 像主事人会去做的事吗?
Does that sound like someone who has a plan?
那为何Jacob说你知道后续步骤 如果...
Why would Jacob say you knew what to do if...
因为他说的一切都是谎言
Because everything he ever said is a lie.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
Jack 你想不想听个秘密?
You wanna know a secret, Jack?
一个我知道多年的秘密?
Something I've known a long, long time?
你死了
You're dead.
- 你是在打比喻吗?  - 不 我说的就是字面上的意思
- You mean that figuratively, right?  - No. I mean, literally.
我们都死了... 包括这里的每一个人
We're all dead... every single one of us.
至于这里? 这里的... 一切? 并不是你们看到的这样
And this? This... all this? It's not what you think it is.
我们没在岛上 我们从来没上过岛
We're not on an island. We never were.
我们在地狱
We're in hell.
所以我对Jacob说的话 一点儿兴趣也没有
So I'm not interested in what Jacob said.
事实上 或许我们该把他的话抛之耳后
In fact, maybe it's time we stopped listening to him
转而去听其他人的
and we started listening to someone else.
我也正打算这么做
And that's exactly what I'm gonna do.
迷失 第6季第9集
你在干嘛?
What're you doing?
- 我去把Richard追回来  - 追他干嘛? 你听到他说的话了
- I'm going after Richard.  - Why? You heard him.
他不... 他不知道我们接下来该干嘛
He doesn't... he doesn't know what we need to do next.
他知道 Jacob跟我说过 他知道的
He knows. Jacob told me. He has to know.
Alpert精神不正常
Alpert has lost his mind.
他以为我们... 我们身处地狱
He thinks that we're... we're in hell.
如果他在乎Jacob说的话
And if he care about what Jacob said,
他不会说... 去听别人的话
he wouldn't be talking about... about listening to someone else.
等等
Wait.
你知道他指的是谁?
You know who he meant?
哦 这下好玩了
Oh, this should be interesting.
什么
What?
他是指Locke
He meant Locke.
Locke死了啊
Locke is dead.
他指的不是真正的Locke 如果这能安抚你的话
If it's any consolation, it's not exactly Locke.
Hurley啊
Hurley.
他在说什么?
What's he sayin'?
呃 谁... 在说什么?
Uh, wh... what's who saying?
- Jacob 我看到你在跟他说话  - 我没在和Jacob说话
- Jacob. I saw you talking to him.  - I'm not talking to Jacob.
别骗我 拜托 如果你知道些什么...
Don't lie to me. Please, if you know something...
- 或者任何能帮我们走出困境...  - 兄弟 和我说话的不是Jacob
- Anything that can help us figure out...  - It's not Jacob, man.
那是谁?
Then who is it?
抱歉 Jack 这与你无关
Sorry, Jack, but this has nothing to do with you.
- Shephard说得没错  - 没说错什么?
- Shephard is right, you know.  - Right about what?
Richard 追他回来只是浪费时间
Richard. Going after him is a waste of time.
他什么都不知道
He doesn't know anything.
- 你怎么这么肯定?  - 我12岁起就认识他了
- What makes you so sure?  - I've known him since I was 12 years old.
这多少也能说明些事吧
That should count for something.
你们还是孩子的时候 就认识了?
So you guys met when you were kids, huh?
不 Frank 那时我年纪尚小
No, Frank, I was a kid.
而Richard的模样 却和今天别无二致
Richard looked just like he does today.
你是说他长生不老?
You're saying this guy doesn't age?
我就是这个意思
That's exactly what I'm saying.
那你觉得这到底是怎么回事?
And how the hell do you think that happened?
1867年 加那利群岛之一 特尼里弗岛
Ricardo 你是吗?
嗯 是我
Isabella 你继续睡吧
你发烧了...
我没事
我去找医生
上帝保佑 我天亮前回来
希望能赶得及
把这个给医生吧...
不 Isabella...
拿着吧 亲爱的
要是你有什么意外的话...
闭上眼
我们的心永远在一起
我不会让你有事的
你不能进去!
你不能进来...
抱歉 但我等不及了
我妻子病得很重 大夫
给他几床毯子
谢谢您 大夫
不是给你的...
你身上的水 滴到我地板上了
我妻子在咳血...
她需要您... 求您了 大夫
你们住在哪儿?
El Socorro附近
El Socorro吗?
到那儿要半天呢
这种倾盆大雨的日子
一路上我可受不了
我有药...
可以救她的命...
但要价很高
嗯 没问题 能救她就行 谢谢您 大夫
你只有这点儿钱?
就只有这些了
这东西一钱不值
求求您 求求您 大夫...
我可以做工还债的 求求您了!
别拉着我!
放手!
Isabella啊
Isabella.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
Isabella啊
Isabella.
不!
No!
我给你带了点儿吃的 孩子
我不饿 神父
或许待会儿就饿了呢
你那本"圣经" 可以给我看一下吗?
是英语版的啊
嗯... 我在自学
Isabella... 我妻子和我曾想去"新世界"旅游
我们想生个孩子
开始新生活
你准备好忏悔了吗?
神父 请原谅我犯下的罪行
神父 我...
杀了人
我罪孽深重
神父 求求您...
请上帝宽恕我吧
不
No.
什么?
你犯的是谋杀罪 我不能赦免你
神父 那只是个意外
我不是故意要杀他的
但你的确把他杀了
求求您 神父...
一定还有别的方式 能得到上帝的宽恕
要重获上帝的恩宠 只有以苦行赎罪
嗯 这是肯定的... 我什么都愿意做
可是你没时间赎罪了
因为明天
你就要上绞刑架了
可怜啊 孩子...
恐怕魔鬼 早已在地狱等着你了
愿上帝宽恕你的灵魂
把他的眼睛蒙起来
是这个人吗?
Is this him?
没错
Yes.
安静
Estate quieto.
你说 他会说英语
You say he speaks English.
是的 Whitfield先生
Yes, Mr. Whitfield.
你会说英语吗?
Do you speak English?
我在问你 会不会说英语?
I asked, do you speak English?
把他带走 换一个人过来
Take him away and bring me another.
- 给他去受绞刑吧  - 会 我会说! 我会说!
- Hang him.  - Yes, I speak it! Yes, I speak it!
等等
Wait.
你的手挺粗壮的 过去是干什么的?
You have strong hands. What sort of work did you do?
我... 我是做... 我是做... 我... 在地里劳作
I... I work... I work... I... in the fields.
听说你想去"新世界" 是吗?
I understand you're interested in going to the New World. Yes?
是的
Yes.
好 那么...
Well, then...
今天就是你的幸运日 谢谢你 神父
This is your lucky day. Thank you, Father.
这个人现在归Magnus Hanso船长所有了
This man is now the property of Captain Magnus Hanso.
希望你别晕船哦
I hope you don't get seasick.
你看见什么了吗?
太黑了
等等 我看见陆地了!
我看见海岸了
是个岛
我看见了魔鬼!
这个岛是魔鬼的领地!
上帝宽恕我们了
至少宽恕了部分人
看见什么东西了吗?!
Do you see anything?!
- 把船长给我找来  - 长官 Hanso船长死了
- Bring me the captain.  - Sir, Captain Hanso's dead.
天啊 我们身陷诡谲丛林之中!
Good God, we're in the middle of a bloody jungle!
我们在下面!
救救我们!
我们还活着!
我们在下面!
Down here, please!
- 救命!  - 到下面来! 拜托!
- Help!  - Down here! Please!
我们在下面!
- 到下面来啊! 救救我们!  - 我们在这里啊?
- Down here! Please help us!  - Estamos aqu?
- 我们在这里啊?  - 到下面来啊!
- Estamos aqu?  - Down here!
感谢上帝
Gracias a dios. Gracias.
谢天谢地
Muchas gracias.
不!
No!
不! 住手! 住手!
No! Stop! No!
不! 住手!
No! Stop!
- 不 不  - 别 别 别
- No. No.  - No, no, no.
不! 住手!
No! Stop!
啊!
Aah!
- 你要干什么?!  - 啊!
- What are you doing?!  - Aah!
求求你
Se lo ruego.
别这样做
No lo haga.
求你了 别杀我
No lo haga, por favor.
我们的船在丛林中撞毁
We are shipwrecked in the middle of the jungle.
我们没有水源
We have no fresh water
补给有限
and limited supplies,
只剩下五个船员
and there are only five officers left.
不! 不! 不!
No! No! No!
为什么... 你为什么要这么做?
Why... why are you doing this?
因为如果我放了你们
Because if I freed you,
时间一长
it would only be a matter of time
你们就会杀了我
before you tried to kill me.
不!
No!
上面发生什么事了?
What happened up there?
跟我汇报!
I said report!
出去!
我会杀了你的!
喂?
有人吗?
有... 有! 我在这儿!
是Isabella?
Ricardo啊...
我不明白... 你怎么... 在这儿?
你还不明白吗 Ricardo? 我们死了 两个人都死了
我们在地狱
我得在他回来之前 救你出去
什么?
在谁回来之前?
恶魔
恶魔?
我从他的眼睛里... 看到的就是魔鬼
你见过他吗 Ricardo?
是 我想我见过...
我们得离开这儿...
快走!
快走 马上!
亲爱的 快走!
快走 现在就走!
我不能...
亲爱的 我说过我不会让你有事的!
我说过不让你有事 就不要你出事 亲爱的
求你了!
我怕...
如果你爱我 就快走!
快走!
不 不
No, no.
放开她!
求你放开她!
Isabella啊!
Isabella!
别怕 看这儿
Shh. Here.
喝点水
Water.
谁...
Who...
谁... 你是谁?
Who... who are you?
一个朋友
A friend.
我是...
I am...
在地狱吗?
in hell?
是的 恐怕是的
Yes, I'm afraid you are.
你...
You...
你不是船上的人
You are not on the ship.
早在你们的船失事之前...
I was here...
我就在这个岛上待着了
long before your ship.
你... 你...
Did... did...
你看到我的... 我的妻子没?
did you see my... my wife?
- 谁?  - Isabella 我妻子
- I'm sorry?  - Isabella. My wife.
她本来在这里 她...
She was here. She was...
但... 后来那股黑烟来了
But... then the black smoke came,
她就跑开了
and she ran.
然后再没回来?
And she hasn't come back?
那也许代表他抓住了她
That probably mean he has her.
谁?
Who?
我想你知道是谁
I think you know who.
如果她还活... 活着 我得救她
If she's a... alive, I must save her.
求你 拜托 帮帮我
Please. Please, help me.
当然 当... 当然我会帮忙
Of course. Of... of course I'll help.
我也想要自由
I want to be free, too.
碰巧...
As luck would have it...
我在外面船员的身上 找到了这个
I found these on one of the officers outside.
我想我可以打开你的锁
I think they'll work.
但是在我开锁之前 你得答应帮我
But before I try, I need to know that you will help me.
好的 好的 当... 当然
Yes. Yes. Of... of course.
我说什么 你都会照做吗?
You'll do anything I ask?
是的 是的 一切照做 我发誓
Yes. Yes, anything. Yes, I promise.
那就成交
Then we're agreed.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气 我的朋友
Of course, my friend.
很高兴见到你 脱离锁链的束缚
It's good to see you out of those chains.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们得让你先站起来
Let's get you on your feet.
如果我们打算逃离 你得先恢复力气
You're gonna need your strenth if we're going to escape.
逃离?
Escape?
对的
That's right.
要逃离地狱 恐怕只有一条路
I'm afraid there's only one way to escape from hell.
你得杀了那个恶魔
You're going to have to kill the devil.
等你吃完
When you're finished eating,
你就朝西一直走
you'll walk due west.
一旦你走到海边
Once you get to the ocean,
就能看到雕像
you'll be able to see the statue.
雕像?
The statue?
你们的船在开进来的时候 撞上它了
Your ship smashed through it on its way inland.
把它撞得粉碎
Broke it into pieces.
在那儿 你能找到那个恶魔
That's where you'll find the devil.
你只有一次机会
You only have one chance.
把这个刺进他的胸膛
Put this through his chest.
别犹豫 别让他开口说一个字
Do not hesitate. Do not let him say a word.
如果他一开口 就晚了
If he speaks, it will already be too late.
他很擅长游说
He can be very persuasive.
我... 我怎么能用这个杀了他?
How... how can I kill him with this?
他... 他是... 一股黑烟
He... he is... black smoke.
不
No.
我才是
I am.
我的妻子Isabella...
My wife Isabella...
她是想躲开你?
She was running from you?
她是想躲开他
She was running from him.
对不起 我看到他把她带走
I'm sorry. I saw him take her,
但是我阻止不了他
but I couldn't do anything to stop him.
但是... 但如果你是那股黑烟 你...
But... but if you are the black smoke, you...
朋友 不止你一个人失去了重要的东西
You aren't the only one who's lost something, my friend.
那个恶魔背叛了我
The devil betrayed me.
他拿走了我的肉身
He took my body,
我的人性
My humanity.
你... 你杀了船上那些船员
You... you killed the officers on the ship.
你该担心的人不是我
I'm not the one you need to worry about.
是那个恶魔带走了你的妻子
The devil has your wife,
如果你想抢回她
and you are going to have to kill him
就必须杀了他
if you ever want to get her back.
谋杀是不对的 它让我饱尝了今日的恶果
Murder is wrong. That is what brought me here.
我的朋友...
My friend...
咱俩可以花一整天 来讨论什么是对 什么是错
You and I can talk all day long about what's right or wrong.
但你面对的问题 始终如一
But the question before you remains the same.
你到底还想不想 再见到你的妻子?
Do you ever want to see your wife again?
嗯 我想
Yes, I do.
啊!
Uhh!
你在这儿干嘛?! 谁给你的这个?!
What're you doing here?! Who gave you this?!
我妻子在哪?
Where is my wife?
什么?
What?
我妻子在哪?
Where is my wife?
我... 我不认识你妻子
I... I don't know your wife.
- 她乘这艘船过来的吗?  - 不 她死了
- Did she come here on the ship?  - No. She's dead.
那你为什么问我她在哪?
Then why are you asking me where she is?
你在丛林里 有遇见一个黑衣人吗?
Did you meet a man in the jungle dressed in black?
是的
Yes.
他跟你说了什么?
What did he tell you?
他说你是恶魔
He said you are the devil.
然后呢?
And?
他说我只有杀了你
He said the only way I would see my wife again
才能再见到我的妻子
is if I kill you.
我... 我在这里看到她...
I... I saw her here...
就在这儿 她在哪儿?!
In this place. Where is she?!
- 那不是你的妻子  - 是的 那就是!
- That wasn't your wife.  - Yes, it was!
- 她死了 跟我一样  - 你没死
- She is dead, just like me.  - You're not dead.
我... 我在地狱 我知道我在地狱!
I... I am in hell. I know that I am in hell!
- 你真认为你已经死了?  - 要不我现在是在哪?
- You really think you're dead?  - Where else would I be?
那好
All right then.
你要干嘛? 你要干嘛?
What are you doing? What are you doing?
不 不 不 不!
No, no, no, no!
- 还认为你已经死了?!  - 啊!
- Still think you're dead?!  - Aah!
啊!
Aah!
- 还认为你已经死了?!  - 住手!
- Still think you're dead?!  - Stop!
我为什么要住手?!
Why should I stop?!
因为我不想死!
Because I want to live!
这是你说过的唯一清醒的话
That's the first sensible thing you've said.
你叫什么?
What's your name?
我叫Ricardo
Ricardo.
好 Ricardo
起来 我们得聊聊
Get up. We need to talk.
那里面有什么?
What is inside?
除非我邀请 否则谁也别想进去
No one comes in unless I invite them in.
你是恶魔吗?
Are you the devil?
不
No.
那你是谁?
Then who are you?
我叫Jacob
My name is Jacob.
是我 把你们的船引到这岛上来的
I'm the one who brought your ship to this island.
你把我们弄过来的?
You brought it here?
为什么?
Why?
把这瓶酒 想象成你一直说的"地狱"
Think of this wine as what you keep calling "Hell."
它还有很多别名
There's many other names for it, too.
"恶毒"
"Malevolence."
"邪恶"
"Evil."
"黑暗"
"Darkness."
看这儿 它在瓶子里打转
And here it is, swirling around in the bottle,
却出不去
unable to get out,
因为如果它出去了 它就会到处肆虐
because if it did, it would spread.
这个软木塞...
The cork...
就好比这座小岛
is this island.
只有它能够将黑暗势力困在...
And it's the only thing keeping the darkness...
它该在的地方
where it belongs.
那个派你来杀我的男人
That man who sent you to kill me
认为所有人都是堕落的
believes that everyone is corruptible
因为人性本恶
because it's in their very nature to sin.
我把人们引到这岛上来 想证明他是错的
I bring people here to prove him wrong.
一旦他们到了这里 他们的过去就不再重要了
And when they get here, their past doesn't matter.
在你把我的船引到这儿以前 还有过其他人?
Before you brought my ship, there were others?
对 有很多
Yes. Many.
- 他们后来怎么样了?  - 他们都死了
- What happened to them?  - They're all dead.
可如果是你把他们弄来的 你为什么不帮他们?
But if you brought them here, why didn't you help them?
因为我希望他们能自力更生...
Because I wanted them to help themselves...
学会明辨是非
to know the difference between right and wrong
而不是非得由我去告诉他们
without me having to tell them.
如果我强迫他们去做事情 那一切就没意义了
It's all meaningless if I have to force them to do anything.
我为什么非得插手呢?
Why should I have to step in?
你要是不插手 他就会插手啊
If you don't, he will.
你想找个活儿干吗?
Do you want a job?
什么? 找个活儿?
What? A job?
干什么?
Doing what?
嗯...
Well...
如果我不想插手这档子事
If I don't want to step in,
也许你可以替我援助他们
maybe you can do it for me.
你可以做我的... 我的代表...
You can be my... my representative...
做我和那些人的中间人
an intermediary between me and the people
- 那些被我带到岛上的人  - 那 我能换到什么好处?
- I bring to the island.  - Well, what will I get in return?
- 随你说  - 我想要我妻子活过来
- You tell me.  - I want my wife back.
我做不到
Can't do that.
你能赦免我的罪过 让我不用下地狱吗?
Can you absolve me of my sins so I don't go to hell?
这我也办不到
I can't do that either.
那我永远也不想死 我... 我想永生
Then I never want to die. I... I want to live forever.
这个
Now that...
我答应你
I can do.
你让他开口说话了 是吗?
You let him talk to you, didn't you?
他让我给你这个
He told me to give you this.
我想你明白 要是你跟他走
I'm sure you realize that if you go with him,
你就再也见不到你的妻子了
you'll never be with your wife again.
我理解
I understand.
他很擅长...
He can be very...
游说人
convincing.
但我想让你知道 如果你改变主意...
But I want you to know if you ever change your mind...
我是说不论何时...
and I mean ever...
我和你的交易始终有效
my offer still stands.
我有样东西要给你
I have something for you.
你肯定是不小心弄掉了
You must have dropped it.
我在船上找到的
I found it on the ship.
亲爱的 再见了
我改变主意了
I've changed my mind.
你听见了吗?
Are you listening to me?
我改变主意了
I've changed my mind.
我以前错了!
I was wrong!
你说过 我可以改变主意的
You said I could change my mind.
你说过 交易始终有效的!
You said the offer would stand!
那个交易还算数吗?
Does the offer still stand?
那个交易还算数吗?!
Does the offer still stand?!
什么交易 老兄?
What offer, dude?
你怎么会在这儿? 你跟踪我?
What the hell are you doing out here? Did you follow me?
- 嗯 差不多  - 走... 走开! 滚!
- Well, kinda.  - Get.. get out! Get out!
喂!
Hey!
- 你没... 你没听见我说的吗?!  - 我只是...
- Did... didn't you hear what I said?!  - Look, I was just...
- 我跟你们的人说了 我什么也不知道!  - 老兄 冷静点!
- I told you people, I don't know anything!  - Dude, just calm down!
- 你干嘛跟踪我?!  - 是你妻子让我来的!
- Why did you follow me?!  - Your wife sent me!
你说什么?
What did you say?
我说 是你妻子让我来的 Isabella啊
I said your wife sent me. Isabella.
她想知道 你为什么把她的十字架埋起来
She wants to know why you buried her cross.
你... 你是怎么知道的?
H... how do you know about that?
- 因为是她刚才告诉我的  - 什么叫 刚才告诉你的?
- Because she just told me.  - What do you mean, just told you?
Isabella看见你把十字架挖出来了 老兄
Isabella saw you dig it up, man.
她现在就站在你身边
She's standing right next to you.
他不相信你
有时候 人们需要点儿时间才会相信
我... 我... 我看不见她
I... I... I don't see her.
告诉他 他英文说得很好
她就在那儿
She's right there.
她说你的英语很棒
She says your English is awesome.
你... 真的在这儿吗?
闭上眼睛
Cierra tus ojos.
她想让你闭上眼睛
She wants you to close your eyes.
没关系的 我会告诉你她说了什么
It's okay. I'll tell you what she says.
No fue tu culpa que yo mor, Ricardo.
我的死不是你的错 Ricardo
就像你非常想救我一样...
只是我的日子到头了
你受了很多苦 Ricardo
我想你...
为了我俩能重聚 我愿意做任何事
我的爱人
我们已经在一起了
她走了?
Is she gone?
嗯
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗯 不用客气
Yeah, you got it.
有什么不对劲吗?
Something wrong?
嗯 她还说了一件事
Well, she kinda said one more thing.
一件你非做不可的事
Something you have to do.
什么事?
What?
她说你得阻止那个黑衣人
She said you have to stop the man in black.
你得阻止他离开这座岛
You have to stop him from leaving the island.
因为如果你不这样做...
'Cause if you don't...
我们都会下地狱
早上好
Good morning.
早
Morning.
看来 你收到我的礼物了
I see you got my present.
别沾沾自喜 Jacob 这东西可不是你
Don't gloat, Jacob. It doesn't become you.
所以你想要杀我
So you tried to kill me.
你想要什么 一个道歉?
What do you expect, an apology?
不
No.
我想 我只是好奇你为什么要这么做
I guess I'm just wondering why you did it.
因为我想离开这儿
Because I want to leave.
你就让我走吧 Jacob
Just let me leave, Jacob.
只要我还活着 你哪儿也别想去
As long as I'm alive, you're not going anywhere.
哦 那现在 你知道我为什么想杀你了
Well, then now you know why I want to kill you.
我会杀了你的 Jacob
And I will kill you, Jacob.
就算你杀了我 也会有别人接替我的位置
Even if you do, somebody else will take my place.
哦 那我就把他们也杀了
Well, then I'll kill them, too.
给
Here.
帮你消磨时光
Something for you to pass the time.
回头见
I'll see you around.
再见不会太久的
Sooner than you think.